[OCEAN WAVES CRASHING & WIND HOWLING]
[EERIE MYSTERIOUS THEME MUSIC]
[ATMOSPHERIC SILENCE]
[DISTANT SEAGULLS & BREAKING WAVES]
[DARK CINEMATIC STRINGS]
[FOOTSTEPS CRUNCHING ON WET SAND]
[SPEAKER_01] Gone... gone... gone!
[OCEAN SWELL ROARING]
[CHILLING SILENCE]
[SPEAKER_02] Whoever wears the crown,
their hands will bear the blood.
[TENSE STRINGS SWELLING]
[SPEAKER_01] Even with this sea water,
these hands cannot be washed, Laila.
[SPEAKER_03] The lust for power is perilous Mandaar,
once touched, there is no return.
[THUNDERCLAP & CRASHING TIDES]
[SPEAKER_01] I do not want to return.
I want to see the end.
[EERIE SILENCE]
[SPEAKER_02] Then be prepared Mandaar,
destiny forgives no one.
[CLOSING THEME & CRASHING OCEAN WAVES]